Mss.B.F327
American Philosophical Society
- William Smallwood to Henry Hollingsworth, 1778 April 8; No. 1274
- Benjamin Smith and Samuel Smith, 1776 October 31; No. 1275
- Christopher Smith to Evert Bancker, 1778 January 26; No. 1276
- Christopher Smith to Evert Bancker, 1778 January 29; No. 1277
- Christopher Smith to Evert Bancker, 1778 August 19; No. 1278
- Christopher Smith to Evert Bancker, 1778 August 31; No. 1279
- Christopher Smith to Evert Bancker, 1778 September 27; No. 1280
- Christopher Smith to Evert Bancker, 1778 November 15; No. 1281
- Christopher Smith to Evert Bancker, 1778 December 7; No. 1282
- Ezra Smith to Andrew Adams, 1782 January 8; No. 1283
- Francis Smith to the Officers of the Ordinance at Quebec, 1770 November 15; No. 1284
- James Smith to Mathew Dill, 1781 December 27; No. 1285
- James Smith to Mr. ______ McKennen, 1778 March 28; No. 1286
- John Smith to William Logan, 1756 June 14; No. 1287
- Jonathan Bayard Smith and Jacob Morris to Joseph Reed, 1781 January 22; No. 1288
- Smith, Melancton, and Company to the Fourth Massachusetts Regiment, 1783 April; No. 1289
- Samuel Smith to James A. Buchanan, 1824 December 15; No. 1290
- Samuel Smith to Abel James and Cadwallader Morris and Company, 1780 January 15; No. 1291
- Samuel Smith, Andrew Kirchline, and John Lacey, sublieutenants to the substitutes at Coryell's Ferry, N.J., 1777 July 12; No. 1292
- Thomas Smith to Barnard Gratz, 1780 December 9; No. 1293
- Thomas Smith to Jasper Yeates, 1803 August 8; No. 1294
- William Stephens Smith, 1802 March 22; No. 1295
- William Stephens Smith, 1803 May 4; No. 1296
- William Stephens Smith to John Sullivan, 1786 December 6; No. 1297
- Benjamin Seaman and Francis Barretto, 1803 May 10; No. 1298
- Society for the Institution and Support of First Day or Sunday Schools to David Jackson, 1794 July 29; No. 1299
- Society of the Cincinnati to Aaron Aorson, 1785 December 10; No. 1300
- Society of the Cincinnati, 1784 May 17; No. 1301
- Society of Friends, 1776 September 28; No. 1302
- Society of Friends, 1775 January 24; No. 1303
- State of South Carolina to the sheriff, 1784 January 6; No. 1304
- Selectmen of Connecticut, Town of Mansfield, 1776 February-July; No. 1305
- John Spencer to Comfort Wheaton, 1777 June 30; No. 1306
- Jonathan Grout, 1781 August 7; No. 1307
- Alexander Spotswood to Bushrod Washington, 1807 February 14; No. 1308
- Colony of Virginia, Spotsylvania County to James Sparks, Thomas Minor, and Joseph Holladay, 1754 July 2; No. 1309
- Samuel Spring to George Bliss, 1815 February 3; No. 1310
- Joseph Stafford to F.F. Stockwell, 1859 April 6, 23; No. 1311
- Stamp Act, 1766-1775; No. 1312
- Caleb Stark to Samuel Blodger, 1784 October 27; No. 1313
- Ebenezer Stearns to John Fisher, 1737/38 January 10; No. 1314
- Joseph Stedham, sheriff to William Hemphill, 1785 September 29; No. 1315
- Benjamin Stelle, 1778 February 28; No. 1316
- Friedrich Wilhelm, baron von Steuben, 1786 April 23; No. 1317
- Friedrich Wilhelm, baron von Steuben to Pierre-Etienne (Peter Stephen) du Ponceau, 1778 June 30; No. 1318
- Friedrich Wilhelm, baron von Steuben to Samuel Huntington, 1784 October 14; No. 1319
- Friedrich Wilhelm, baron von Steuben to Eleanor-Francois-Elie, marquis de Moustier, 1789?; No. 1320
- Friedrich Wilhelm, baron von Steuben to William North, 1789 July 25; No. 1321
- Friedrich Wilhelm, baron von Steuben to Richard Peters?, 1788 March 7; No. 1322
- Daniel Stevens to John F. Grimke, 1799 June 1; No. 1323
- Ebenezer Stevens to Samuel Doggett, 1776 September 8; No. 1324
- Edward Stevens to Thomas Jefferson, 1781 February 11; No. 1325
- Cornell Stevenson, 1776 August 5; No. 1326
- Abraham Stewart to John Fisher, 1778 September 4; No. 1327
- Alexander Stewart and Alexander MacLean to the President (Richard Caswell) and members of Congress now sitting at Halifax, N.C., 1776 November 10; No. 1328
- John Stiles, Jr. to John Hancock, 1771 August 6; No. 1329
- Richard Stockton and Joseph Stockton to Thomas Stockton, 1771 April 15; No. 1330
- Benjamin Stoddert to Henry Hollingsworth, 1780 January 13; No. 1331
- Benjamin Stoddert to Henry Hollingsworth, 1780 February 3; No. 1332
- Benjamin Stoddert to Henry Hollingsworth, 1780 February 26; No. 1333
- Benjamin Stoddert to Henry Hollingsworth, 1780 June 26; No. 1334
- Garrit Storm to Henry J. Bleecker, 1799 December 30; No. 1335
- Thomas Storm to Henry J. Bleeker, 1799 December 30; No. 1336
- Thomas Storm to Henry J. Bleeker, 1800 January 3; No. 1337
- George Story to Hervey Luce, 1820 July 11; No. 1338
- John Sullivan to William Palfrey, 1778 March 11; No. 1339
- John Sullivan to Benjamin Stelle, 1778 October 27; No. 1340
- John Sullivan to George Washington, 1778 August 19; No. 1341
- Alexander Sutherland, 1781 October 25-December 24; No. 1342
- James Swan to M. de la Grange, 1808 May 1; No. 1343
- Benjamin Tallmadge to Benjamin Bourne, 1792 November 19; No. 1344
- Banastre Tarleton to Messrs. Byfield, 1805 August 18; No. 1345
- Henry Taylor, 1776 September 15; No. 1346
- Timothy Taylor to Samuel Coates, 1782 October 27; No. 1347
- Joseph Tell to John Jacob Able, 1749 September 15, October 3; No. 1348
- Nathaniel Thacher to Henry Jackson, 1778 December 27; No. 1349
- John Thomas and others to All whom it may concern, 1782 July 6; No. 1350
- Sarah D. Thomas to Sylvester Dering, 1785 November 21; No. 1351
- Sarah D. Thomas to Elizabeth Dering, 1781 May 17; No. 1352
- Sarah D. Thomas to Elizabeth Dering, 1781?; No. 1353
- Sarah D. Thomas to Mary Dering, 1785 November 20; No. 1354
- Sarah D. Thomas to Sylvester Dering, 1805 June 7; No. 1355
- Andrew Thompson to Samuel Logan, 1783 April 29; No. 1356
- William Thompson to the Pennsylvania Council of Safety, 1777 January 12; No. 1357
- William Thompson to Matthew Irwin, n.d.; No. 1358
- William Thompson to Robert Morris, 1777 October 16; No. 1359
- William Thompson to Colonel _______, n.d.; No. 1360
- William Thompson to the Fourth Massachusetts Regiment, 1783 May 26; No. 1361
- United States, Continental Congress (Charles Thomson, secretary) to the General (Benjamin Lincoln) commanding in the Southern Department, 1778 October 13; No. 1362
- United States, Continental Congress (Charles Thomson, secretary), 1779 October 6, 7; No. 1363
- United States, Continental Congress (Charles Thomson, secretary), 1780 February 9; No. 1364
- Charles Thomson to Robert Rutherford, 1765 November 6; No. 1365
- Tench Tilghman to Clement Biddle, 1778? January-February; No. 1366
- Tench Tilghman to John Chaloner, 1778 July 23; No. 1367
- Tench Tilghman to Tobias Fernald, 1782 December 2; No. 1368
- Tench Tilghman to John Fitzgerald, 1784 November 5; No. 1369
- Richard Tilghman to Philip? Francis, 1773 September 29; No. 1370
- Daniel Tillinghast to William Greene, 1777 April 18; No. 1371
- Jonathan Titcomb to Solomon Lovell, 1779 July 21; No. 1372
- Edward Tobin to Friedrich Wilhelm, baron von Steuben, 1782; No. 1373
- Lewis Tousard to James McHenry, 1799 December 23; No. 1374
- Lord George Townshend to Richard Temple Grenville, Lord Temple, 1782 August 4; No. 1375
- Dominick Trant to Henry Jackson, 1782 April 16; No. 1376
- Raimonde Trentenova to Robert Goodloe Harper, 1822 August 1; No. 1377
- Robert Troup to William Cadman, 1798 October 29; No. 1378
- Officers of Connecticut Regiments to Jonathan Trumbull, 1778 July 30; No. 1379
- American Academy of Fine Arts, n.d.; No. 1380
- Jonathan Trumbull to the civil authority, selectmen, committee of inspection, and all military officers in the town of Woodstock, Conn., 1776 August 1; No. 1381
- John Trumbull to Peter Augustus Jay, 1798 August 6; No. 1382
- Jonathan Trumbull to Daniel Wadsworth, 1798 April 28; No. 1383
- Jonathan Trumbull to Daniel Wadsworth, 1800 January 2; No. 1384
- Jonathan Trumbull to Jeremiah Wadsworth, 1794 October 22; No. 1385
- Jonathan Trumbull to Jeremiah Wadsworth, 1794 November 7; No. 1386
- Jonathan Trumbull to Jeremiah Wadsworth, 1794 November 15; No. 1387
- Jonathan Trumbull to Jeremiah Wadsworth, 1796 May 19; No. 1388
- Jonathan Trumbull to Jeremiah Wadsworth, 1796 May 21; No. 1389
- Jonathan Trumbull to Jeremiah Wadsworth, 1796 May 28; No. 1390
- Jonathan Trumbull to Jeremiah Wadsworth, 1797 February 20; No. 1391
- Jonathan Trumbull to Jeremiah Wadsworth, 1797 April 4; No. 1392
- Colony of Connecticut, Governor Jonathan Trumbull, 1776 January 18; No. 1393
- Joseph Trumbull to George Washington, 1775 November 20; No. 1394
- Joseph Trumbull to the Continental Congress, 1776 January 23; No. 1395
- Ebenezer Tucker, 1801 June 29; No. 1396
- St. George Tucker to John Page, 1791 July 30; No. 1397
- Samuel Tudor to Philip Schuyler, 1776 September 30; No. 1398
- William Tudor to Stephen Collins, 1775 September 27; No. 1399
- Robert Troup to Messrs. Gouverneur and Kemble, 1802 April 8; No. 1400
- Benjamin Tupper, by order of Gen. Levi Shephard to the selectmen of Long Meadow, Mass., 1787 January 27; No. 1401
- H______ Turnbill to Moses Woodward, 1781 September 8; No. 1402
- William Turner to John Hancock, 1788 September 15; No. 1403
- John Steel Tyler to Henry Jackson, 1778 February 3; No. 1404
- John Steel Tyler to Henry Jackson, 1778 February 6; No. 1405
- John Steel Tyler to Henry Jackson, 1778 February 12; No. 1406
- John Steel Tyler to Henry Jackson, 1778 February 17; No. 1407
- John Steel Tyler to Henry Jackson, 1778 March 4; No. 1408
- John Steel Tyler to Henry Jackson, 1778 June 14; No. 1409
- John Steel Tyler to Henry Jackson, 1778 September; No. 1410
- John Steel Tyler to Henry Jackson, 1778 September 15; No. 1411
- John Steel Tyler to Henry Jackson, 1778 September 26; No. 1412
- John Steel Tyler to Henry Jackson, 1778 September; No. 1413
- John Steel Tyler to Henry Jackson, 1778 October 5; No. 1414
- John Steel Tyler to Henry Jackson, 1778 November 3; No. 1415
- John Steel Tyler to Henry Jackson, 1778 November 25; No. 1416
- John Steel Tyler to Henry Jackson, 1778 December 1; No. 1417
- John Steel Tyler to Henry Jackson, 1778 December 14, 17; No. 1418
- John Steel Tyler to Henry Jackson, 1778 December 30; No. 1419
- Cornelius Thomas to Elias B. Dayton, 1800 June 3; No. 1420
- Samuel Bayard, 1779-1781; No. 1421
- United States, Continental Army, 1777 March 10; No. 1422
- Friedrich Wilhelm, baron von Steuben, 1780 June 13; No. 1423
- Anthony S. Badgley, 1816 October 2; No. 1424
- S______ Demarest, 1816 October 2; No. 1425
- John Nessle, Jr., 1816 June 5; No. 1426
- John Nessle, Jr., 1816 October 2; No. 1427
- United States, Continental Army, 1777 May 27; No. 1428
- Soldiers of United States, Continental Army, Maryland Division to George Washington, 1779 April 9; No. 1429
- Henry Marble, 1782 March; No. 1430
- Officers of United States, Continental Army, New York Line, 1783; No. 1431
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Assembly, late 1783?; No. 1432; 1.0 vol.
- United States, Continental Army, 1783; No. 1433
- United States, Continental Army, n.d.; No. 1434
- United States, Continental Army, Gen. William Heath's division, 1776 December 3-26; No. 1435
- United States, Continental Congress (John Hancock, President) to Henry J. Vanden Burgh, 1776 November 21; No. 1436
- Commonwealth of Pennsylvania, Supreme Executive Council, 1777 August 27; No. 1437
- United States, Continental Congress (Samuel Huntington, President), n.d.; No. 1438
- United States, Continental Congress (John Hancock, President) to the Indians, 1776 June 10; No. 1439
- United States, Marine Office to all captains, commanders, masters, and other officers of armed vessels commissioned by the United States, 1783 March 25; No. 1440
- United States Congress, 1783; No. 1441
- United States Congress, 1788 September 13; No. 1442
- United States, Continental Congress (John Hancock, President), 1776 April 23, June 25; No. 1443
- United States, Continental Congress (John Hancock, President), 1776 July 31; No. 1444
- Officiers of United States, Continental Army, New York Line, 1783; No. 1445
- United States, Continental Congress (John Hancock, President), 1777 January 9; No. 1446
- United States, First Congress, Second and Third Sessions, 1790-1791; No. 1447; 1.0 vol.
- United States, Second Congress, Second Session, 1792 November 5; No. 1448
- United States, Fourth Congress, First Session, 1795 December 7; No. 1449
- James Monroe, 1815 January 27; No. 1450
- United States Congress, 1815 January 27; No. 1451
- United States Loan Office, State of Massachusetts to John Jeffries, 1794 January 22; No. 1452
- United States, President (John Adams) to Henry Waddell, 1798 September 7; No. 1453
- United States, President (John Adams), 1798 March 23; No. 1454
- United States, President (John Adams), 1799 March 6; No. 1455
- United States, President (Thomas Jefferson) to All whom these may concern, 1806 July 12; No. 1456
- United States, President (James Madison) to Tobias Lear, 1814 August 8; No. 1457
- United States, President (James Madison) to Ross Winans, 1821 June 26; No. 1458
- United States, Department of War, 1798-1799; No. 1459
- George A. Baker to Samuel Bayard, 1794 March 28; No. 1460
- United States, Treasurer of Loans (Francis Hopkinson) to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 October 3; No. 1461
- United States, Treasurer of Loans (Francis Hopkinson) to John Harleston, Jr., 1780 December 10; No. 1462
- Alexander Hamilton, Secretary of the Treasury, on behalf of the United States, and Melancton Smith of New York, 1790 March 15; No. 1463
- Benjamin Lincoln to Gasper Beaufort, 1783 June 27; No. 1464
- Thomas Uram, 1777 December 1-31; No. 1465
- Cornelius Van Dyck to Anthony Wayne, 1777 March 8; No. 1466
- Nicholas Van Dyck to the President (Benjamin Franklin) of the Supreme Executive Council of Pennsylvania, 1786 July 14; No. 1467
- Richard Varick to Sebastian Bauman, 1780 September 18; No. 1468
- Richard Varick, 1776 August 6; No. 1469
- Richard Varick to Abraham Van Vechten, 1804 February 1; No. 1470
- New York City, Mayor (Richard Varick), 1790 March 6; No. 1471
- New York City, Mayor's Court (Richard Varick, mayor), 1799 November 20; No. 1472
- Richard Varick, 1796 August 22; No. 1473
- Richard Varick, 1783; No. 1474
- John Vaughan, 1766 February 24-April 24; No. 1475
- Charles Gravier, comte de Vergennes to John Jay, 1780 March 13; No. 1476
- State of Vermont, Governor (Thomas Chittenden), Council and General Assembly to Edward Aikins and six others, 1782 February 25; No. 1477
- Antoine-Charles du Houx, baron de Viomenil to M. de Bar, 1773 January 7; No. 1478
- Antoine-Charles du Houx, baron de Viomenil to _______, 1779 July 31; No. 1479
- Charles-Joseph-Hyacinthe de Houx de Viomenil to M. Le Baron de P___noits, 1822 March 5; No. 1480
- Commonwealth of Virginia, Governor Benjamin Harrison to James Brown, 1782 June 1; No. 1481
- Commonwealth of Virginia, Governor (Patrick Henry) to Benjamin Moody, 1786 May 1; No. 1482
- Commonwealth of Virginia, Governor (Beverley Randolph) to Frederick Paschke, 1787 May 14; No. 1483
- Commonwealth of Virginia, Governor (Edmund Randolph) to John Young, 1788 September 1; No. 1484
- Commonwealth of Virginia, Governor (Henry Lee) to Robert Harvey and James Mason, 1792 May 15; No. 1485
- Commonwealth of Virginia, Governor (Henry Lee) to Henry Lee, assignee of Armistead Churchill, 1792 January 31; No. 1486
- Commonwealth of Virginia, Governor (John Page) to James Davis, 1804 August 9; No. 1487
- Commonwealth of Virginia, Governor (John Tyler) to Dabney Herndon, 1809 January 14; No. 1488
- Inhabitants of Virginia, Jefferson County to Charles Scott, 1791; No. 1489
- Commonwealth of Virginia to the sheriff, 1783 December 15; No. 1490
- Commonwealth of Virginia, Surry County Court to Benjamin Harrison, 1782 September; No. 1491
- Francis Wade to Henry Hollingsworth, 1780 April 23; No. 1492
- Jeremiah Wadsworth to Alexander Hamilton, 1797 August 2; No. 1493
- Peleg Wadsworth to Charles L. Wadsworth?, 1799 February 13; No. 1494
- Peleg Wadsworth to Charles L. Wadsworth, 1798 February 18; No. 1495
- Benjamin Walker to the cashier of the Bank of Albany, 1799 July 11; No. 1496
- Benjamin Walker to the cashier of the Bank of Albany, 1805 March 4; No. 1497
- Thomas Walley and Samuel Austin to Henry Jackson, 1782 May 31; No. 1498
- Robert Boyle Walsingham to Paul Henry Curry, 1780 April 23; No. 1499
- Gerard Ogden? Walton to the Vice President of the United States (Aaron Burr), 1804 January 5; No. 1500
- Friedrich Adam Julius, baron von Wangenheim to his brother, baron von Wangenheim, 1777 June 24; No. 1501
- Friedrich Adam Julius, baron von Wangenheim to his brother, baron von Wangenheim, 1779 November 30; No. 1502
- Friedrich Adam Julius, baron von Wangenheim to his brother, baron von Wangenheim, 1780 August 8; No. 1503
- Artemus Ward to Ebenezer Hancock, 1776 August 20; No. 1504
- Artemus Ward to John Thomas, 1775 June 24; No. 1505
- Artemus Ward to Joseph? Ward, 1781 January 1; No. 1506
- Jonathan Ward to John Thomas, 1776 January 6; No. 1507
- Joseph Ward to Benjamin Lincoln, 1779 September 25; No. 1508
- James Warren to John Hancock, 1776 February 10; No. 1509
- Joseph Warren to the commanding officer at the house lately occupied by Francis Borland, 1774 May 21; No. 1510
- Anne Steptoe Washington to Hannah Bushrod, 1774 October 23; No. 1511
- Estate of Augustine Washington, 1762 November 30; No. 1512
- Bushrod Washington to Captain _____ Bliss, 1811 December 24; No. 1513
- Bushrod Washington to the cashier of the Bank of the United States, 1809 July 1; No. 1514
- George Washington, 1774 June-1775 April; No. 1515
- George Washington to Rev. Jonathan Boucher, 1772 May 21; No. 1516
- George Washington to the Commissioners of the Federal City, 1799 August 7; No. 1517
- George Washington to Jacob Read, 1784 November 3; No. 1518
- George Washington, 1774 March 12; No. 1519
- George Washington to Stephen Thacker, 1783 June 9; No. 1520
- George Washington to Daniel Tucker, 1783 June 8; No. 1521
- George Washington to Frederick Wyburt, 1783?; No. 1522
- George Washington to Nathanael Greene, 1779 February 24; No. 1523
- George Washington, 1775; No. 1524
- Regarding George Washington, 1800; No. 1525
- George Washington to John Adams, 1798 July 13; No. 1526
- George Washington to George Baylor, 1777 January 9; No. 1527
- George Washington to George Baylor, 1777 April 25; No. 1528
- George Washington to George Baylor, 1777 August 25; No. 1529
- George Washington to Clement Biddle, 1789 May 18; No. 1530
- George Washington to John Brown, 1775 August 12; No. 1531
- George Washington to George Bryan, 1778 May 28; No. 1532
- George Washington to Edward Carrington, 1795 September 28; No. 1533
- George Washington to Edward Carrington, 1798 October 22; No. 1534
- George Washington to Thomas Clark, 1778 December 6; No. 1535
- George Washington to George Clinton, 1778 October 21; No. 1536
- George Washington to George Clinton, 1779 October 1; No. 1537
- George Washington to George Clinton, 1782 May 5; No. 1538
- George Washington to George Clinton, 1782 October 30; No. 1539
- George Washington to James Clinton, 1781 February 16; No. 1540
- George Washington to the Pennsylvania Council of Safety, 1776 December 18; No. 1541
- George Washington to Elias Dayton, 1780 May 20; No. 1542
- George Washington to William Dobbs, 1781 July 31; No. 1543
- George Washington to James Duane, "1776" 1779 May 26; No. 1544
- George Washington to James Duane, 1780 June 5; No. 1545
- George Washington to David Stewart Erskine, Lord Buchan, 1794 May 26; No. 1546
- George Washington to Charles-Henri-Theodat, comte d'Estaing, 1779 September 13; No. 1547
- George Washington to David Forman, 1781 September 2; No. 1548
- George Washington to John Glover and John Paterson, 1780 November 27; No. 1549
- George Washington to Nathanael Greene, 1779 October 6; No. 1550
- George Washington to Nathanael Greene, 1780 January 27; No. 1551
- George Washington to Nathanael Greene, 1781 April 18; No. 1552
- George Washington to Alexander Hamilton, 1791 October 14; No. 1553
- George Washington to Edward Hand, 1779 March 21; No. 1554
- George Washington to Henry Knox, 1779 November 18; No. 1555
- George Washington to Henry Knox, 1780 December 9; No. 1556
- George Washington to Marie-Joseph-Paul-Yves-Roch-Gilbert du Motier, marquis de Lafayette, 1785 April 12; No. 1557
- George Washington to Rev. John Lathrop, 1788 June 22; No. 1558
- George Washington to Tobias Lear, 1790 November 22; No. 1559
- George Washington to Tobias Lear, 1795 December 25; No. 1560
- George Washington to Charles Lee, 1776 November 24; No. 1561
- George Washington to Henry Lee, 1779 October 30; No. 1562
- George Washington to Mary Digges Lee, 1780 October 11; No. 1563
- George Washington to Alexander McDougall, 1778 March 16; No. 1564
- George Washington to James McHenry, 1782 August 15; No. 1565
- George Washington to James McHenry, 1796 July 11; No. 1566
- George Washington to James McHenry, 1799 February 25; No. 1567
- George Washington to James McHenry, 1799 November 17; No. 1568
- George Washington to William McWhir, 1793 February 17; No. 1569
- George Washington to James Madison, 1794 January 10; No. 1570
- George Washington to James Mercer, 1780 February 25; No. 1571
- George Washington to Dr. John Morgan, 1779 June 24; No. 1572
- George Washington to Robert Morris, 1776 December 14; No. 1573
- George Washington to Battaile Muse, 1785 September 18; No. 1574
- George Washington to Battaile Muse, 1786 August 1; No. 1575
- George Washington to Sir Edward Newenham, 1786 June 10; No. 1576
- George Washington to John Nicholas, 1797 November 30; No. 1577
- George Washington to the Pennsylvania Navy Board, 1778 March 2; No. 1578
- George Washington to John Pierce, Jr., 1780 October 3; No. 1579
- George Washington to George Plater, Charles Carroll, John Cadwalader, and Samuel Chase, 1784 December 11; No. 1580
- George Washington to Jeremiah Powell, 1779 October 4; No. 1581
- George Washington to the Rector William White, Church Wardens, and Vestrymen of the United Episcopal Churches of Christ Church and St. Peter's, 1797 March 2; No. 1582
- George Washington to Joseph Reed, 1780 June 29; No. 1583
- George Washington to Joseph Reed, 1781 May 5, 7; No. 1584
- George Washington to George Reid, 1782 June 15; No. 1585
- George Washington to William Russell, 1799 May 26; No. 1586
- George Washington to Arthur St. Clair, 1780 February 2; No. 1587
- George Washington to Arthur St. Clair, 1781 June 23; No. 1588
- George Washington to Joshua Sands, 1798 July 26; No. 1589
- George Washington to Philip Schuyler, 1784 January 21; No. 1590
- George Washington to General Philip Schuyler, 1789 May 9; No. 1591; Letter thanking General Schuyler for his congratulations concerning Washington's election as President.
  David Library Item Number: 1591
- George Washington to Charles Scott, 1779 October 19; No. 1592
- George Washington to John Morin Scott, 1782 June 10; No. 1593
- George Washington to Abraham Skinner, 1781 August 28; No. 1594
- George Washington to William Smallwood, 1778 February 25; No. 1595
- George Washington to William Smallwood and the Field Officers and Commandants of Regiments in the Maryland Line, 1779 February 16; No. 1596
- George Washington to Rev. G.W. Snyder, 1798 September 25; No. 1597
- George Washington to Alexander Spotswood, 1798 September 14; No. 1598
- George Washington to Friedrich Wilhelm, baron von Steuben, 1782 April 12; No. 1599
- George Washington to Annis Boudinot Stockton, 1783 September 2; No. 1600
- George Washington to David Stuart, 1786 December 6; No. 1601
- George Washington to John Sullivan, 1781 May 29; No. 1602
- George Washington to Benjamin Tallmadge, 1779 October 6; No. 1603
- George Washington to Benjamin Tallmadge, 1779 November 2; No. 1604
- George Washington to William Thornton, 1799 February 15; No. 1605
- George Washington to James Tilghman, Jr., 1774 February 17; No. 1606
- George Washington to Jonathan Trumbull, 1779 September 30; No. 1607
- George Washington to Joseph Trumbull, 1777 April 28; No. 1608